hi all welcome to my channel I started
this channel just to
read exchange files today I'm in uh this
NSC stock exchange
website so to I downloaded the today's
uh Excel
file okay uh I got this exchange files
let's study this I added a filter to
this exchange file now I'm going to
select subject well first I select
acquisition okay we have two
Acquisitions for today let's see what it
is
okay first acquisition from I iig
lambard okay what they are acquiring
let's
[Music]
see
okay they have the Target entity Bank of
veroda Market
cap7
1,78 billion investment in this target
entity does not consider related
transaction
icot may have investment business
related transaction with the target
entity at public sector Bank acquisition
of shares is being made in the r cuse
investment function of the
company Target entity in multiple
Stranges over the p period of
time okay invested in investment
invested in the Target multile over on
January 6 the company had acquired
Chase
0.04 icard is acquiring Bank of Bor post
acquisition
.07
you
okay that's one IC lard let's go to
second
one second one is persistent system
limited let's see what persistent is
acquiring
[Music]
okay uh
yeah
why dated July 13 203 we have by inform
your position system limited has entered
into asset purchase agreement with M so
solution India private limited for
acquisition now identify asset on
January 6 subject to
cation okay let's go down entered into
asset
purchase to acquire select assets from
Soho and subject to customer closing
condition being acquired include select
employees contractors
customer contract annual revenue from
this asset is estimated to 4.9 billion 9
million okay so is Prim business of
providing IT services to
bfsi okay
next
[Music]
okay
condition consider payable acquisition
.94 milon this includes up 3.19 are
maximum 2.48 over 3 years which is
conent retention payment 27 milon for
retention few key employees sh so is not
involed in transtion okay we back soed
in
2016 okay so SCH service software
application development company
specialize in front office
operation for scale of Technology
warehousing business intelligence
positions is
[Music]
acquiring mention okay this 4.9
million okay now we are done with the
acquisition let's
um go
[Music]
for bagging order
okay first is zag I think zag back some
orders let's see what zag has
for Z prepa ocean service has entered
into agreement with kirana Car
Technology private
limited okay what they're offering for
them would provide K technology private
Limited
zag Zoya petty cash and zag sa
okay period is for three years
okay okay they are not mention how much
amount okay they got order from
K okay let's go to what Nesco is
offering
Nasco back let's see
let's
go ni logistic management de company
High proposal for
developing okay name of the ENT National
I logistic management
limited is developing operating
maining own bank chai Express
Corridor okay period of least 30
years
30 months of total
cost 75 for each three
Sid revenue from three sides is 350 for
4 years of
operation 16 go for SI
okay let's go
to ashuka Buon let's see what is
thata
beon
informs Bai
chandi road Private limited own subsid
company has
executed with national highway authority
of India January for the project for the
development of four line economic
corridor
from to Gar section
89 9.
812 133 Kil
okay project is
1,391
CR okay time 9 and 10 days including
Monson
[Music]
okay okay lagging is done let's see what
is
next let's see
bonus okay some kpi has some
bonus let's see what it is
[Music]
okay board of directors company
comment of 6 CR 56
l3,2
two Equity shares of face value by each
as a bonus sh share of one equity share
having face value of each of two
existing
share five members who name appear
members okay they're giving one share
for every two
share okay keep green energy
limited okay I
think yeah that's it
corporate action I would love to study
for every day thank you bye